const questionsArray = [
    {
    "question":"gast",
    "answer":"stomach", 
    "correct":false, 
    "guessed":false,
    "memoryStrength":Number,
    "next":Number
    },
    {
    "question":"cardi",
    "answer":"heard",    
    "correct":false, 
    "guessed":false,
    "memoryStrength":Number,
    "next":Number
    },
    {
    "question":"megal", 
    "answer":"enlarged",   
    "correct":false, 
    "guessed":false,
    "memoryStrength":Number, 
    "next":Number
    },
    {
    "question":"itis",
    "answer": "inflammation",   
    "correct":false, 
    "guessed":false,
    "memoryStrength":Number, 
    "next":Number
    },
    {
    "question":"dermat",
    "answer":"skin",    
    "correct":false, 
    "guessed":false,
    "memoryStrength":Number,
    "next":Number,
    },
    {
    "question":"cerebr",
    "answer":"brain",    
    "correct":false, 
    "guessed":false,
    "memoryStrength":Number,
    "next":Number
    },
    {
    "question":"path",
    "answer":"disease",   
    "correct":false, 
    "guessed":false,
    "memoryStrength":Number,
    "next":Number
    },
    {
    "question":"enter",
    "answer": "intestines",
    "correct":false, 
    "guessed":false,
    "memoryStrength":Number,
    "next":Number
    },
    {
    "question":"aden",
    "answer": "gland",
    "correct":false, 
    "guessed":false,
    "memoryStrength":Number,
    "next":Number
    }, 
    {
    "question":"angi",
    "answer": "vessel",
    "correct":false, 
    "guessed":false,
    "memoryStrength":Number,
    "next":Number
    },
    {
    "question":"oma",
    "answer": "tumor",
    "correct":false, 
    "guessed":false,
    "memoryStrength":Number,
    "next":Number
    },
    {
    "question":"nephr",
    "answer": "kidney",
    "correct":false, 
    "guessed":false,
    "memoryStrength":Number,
    "next":Number
    }, 
    {
    "question":"hepat",
    "answer": "liver",
    "correct":false, 
    "guessed":false,
    "memoryStrength":Number,
    "next":Number
    }, 
    {
    "question":"athr",
    "answer":"joint",
    "correct":false, 
    "guessed":false,
    "memoryStrength":Number,
    "next":Number
    },
    {
    "question":"blephar",
    "answer":"eyelid",
    "correct":false, 
    "guessed":false,
    "memoryStrength":Number,
    "next":Number
    },
    {
    "question":"ologist",
    "answer": "specialist",
    "correct":false, 
    "guessed":false,
    "memoryStrength":Number,
    "next":Number
    },
    {
    "question":"malacia",
    "answer":"soft",
    "correct":false, 
    "guessed":false,
    "memoryStrength":Number, 
    "next":Number
    },
]

module.exports = questionsArray;